KRISHNA PRASAD PANTHI

kpanthi@clemson.edu \$ linkedin.com/in/krishnapanthi \$ github.com/kp-square

SUMMARY

Graduate Student and Research assistant at Clemson University. Software developer with 3 years of experience.

SKILLS

Research Time Series Analysis, Forecast modeling, Deep Learning

Programming Languages
Python, C#, JavaScript, C++, SQL
Libraries and Frameworks
Databases
NET, Node.js, Vue.js, GraphQL, Flask,
MSSQL, MYSQL, Redis, MongoDB
Git, Docker, Visual Studio, Aws, Mixpanel

EDUCATION

MS in Computer Science, Clemson University, South Carolina 2024 spring - Present

Graduate Research Assistant - Hydrosystem and Hydroinformatics research group

Bachelor of Computer Engineering, Pulchowk Campus, IOE, Tribhuvan University 2017 - 2021

Relevant Courses: Programming in C/C++, Data Structures, Operating Systems

RESEARCH EXPERIENCE

Graduate Research Assistant

Clemson University, SC, USA

Jan 2024 - Present

Engaged in advanced time series data analysis for flood forecasting under the mentorship of Associate Professor Dr. Vidya Samadi. This research primarily focuses on developing and implementing cutting-edge deep learning models to predict flood events with high accuracy, contributing valuable insights into environmental science and disaster management.

Skills

- Deep Learning methodologies and their application in environmental science
- Proficient in Time-Series Analysis, with a focus on predictive modeling and data forecasting

INDUSTRY EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer Nov 2021 - Dec 2023

MutualArt

Israel

Worked as a software developer with multitude of technologies. Some of the things I worked on include

• Private Sales System: Led the development of the private sales system, used for collaboration between auction

- Private Sales System: Led the development of the private sales system, used for collaboration between auction houses, MutualArt, and users for the private sales of artworks. Technologies: Vuetify, .Net 6 and SQL Server, GraphQL, AWS, Mixpanel.
- Artwork Recommendation: Upgraded an existing artwork recommendation tool from Python2 to Python3.
- Named Entity Recognition: Worked on a Proof of Concept (POC) of Named Entity Recognition system for auto moderation of web scraped data in Python using Spacy.

PROJECTS

Tracking and recognizing people across multiple video cameras. Trained a light weight EfficientNet model on Market 1501 dataset to identify people across multiple cameras. Made use of Kalman Filter for tracking people. Technologies Used: Python3, Tensorflow 2.x, YOLOv4, EfficientNet

Minesweeper-AI. An AI that plays the minesweeper game using Constraint Satisfaction Problem(CSP). Built using Python3. Demo - Youtube).